[
  {
    "Front": "φαίνω",
    "Back": " vb.: viser; (med.) viser mig, synes"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φανηρός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: synlig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φάρµακον",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: medicin; gift"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φάσκω",
    "Back": " vb.: påstår"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φαῦλος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: ringe"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φείδοµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: sparer"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φέρω",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: bærer"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φεύγω",
    "Back": " vb.: flygter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φηµί",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: siger"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φθάνω",
    "Back": " vb.: kommer først"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φθείρω",
    "Back": " vb.: ødelægger"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φθονέω",
    "Back": " vb.: misunder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φθόνος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: misundelse"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φιλέω",
    "Back": " vb.: elsker, kysser"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φιλία",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: venskab"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φίλος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: ven"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φοβέοµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: frygter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φοβερός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: frygtelig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φόβος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: frygt"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φοιτάω",
    "Back": " vb.: besøger (ofte)"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φονεύς",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: morder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φονέω",
    "Back": " vb.: dræber"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φόνος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: drab"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φορέω",
    "Back": " vb.: bærer"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φόρος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: afgift"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φράζω",
    "Back": " vb.: udpeger"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φρονέω",
    "Back": " vb.: tænker"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φρόνηµα",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: tanke"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φρόνιµος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: tænksom"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φροντίζω",
    "Back": " vb.: tænker"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φυγάς",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m./f.: flygtning"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φυγή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: flugt"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φυλακή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: bevogtning"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φύλαξ",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: vogter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φυλάττω",
    "Back": " vb.: vogter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φύσις",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: natur"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φυτόν",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: plante"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φύω",
    "Back": " vb.: lader gro"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φωνέω",
    "Back": " vb.: giver lyd"
  },
  {
    "Front": "φωνή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: stemme"
  }
]